Can I take a few pictures?
ちょっといっぱい撮っていい?
Have you ever done anything naughty with your boyfriend while filming something like this?
彼氏とさ、なんかってこう撮りながらエッチなことしたことある?
do not have.
ない
Isn't there?
ないの?
Yeah.
うん
What should I do if I get photographed?
撮られたらどうするの?
I did it.
やった
That is,
そのことが、
Do you say no?
だ めって言う?
Yeah.
うん
The style is really nice.
スタイルほんといいからさ
Why is that style so good?
なんでそんなストイルいいの?
I haven't done anything yet.
まだ何もしてない
Just exercising?
運動してるだけで?
Yeah.
うん
I want to take the whole body.
全身取りたい
I want to see the back too.
後ろも見たいな
yeah?
ん?
what happened?
どうしたの?
Yeah.
うん
Do you know where the photo was taken?
どこ撮られてるかわかる?
Yeah.
うん
yeah?
ん?
Don't you know?
わかんない?
Yeah.
うん
Ho
ほ
Ra ne.
ら ね
I'm looking inside the skirt.
スカートは中見てるよ
Have you never been told about time or insight?
時間とかさ、 洞察とかされたことないの?
Yeah.
うん
It's not just that you don't notice.
気づかないだけではないんだ
Even though it's cute.
可愛いのに
Try flipping up the skirt.
スカートめくってみて
Because I want to see inside.
中見たいからさ
Look at it.
見してよ
That's a miniskirt.
それミニスカート
Are you wearing pure white?
真っ白履くの?
It's a little see-through under the ribbon.
なんかちょっと透けてんだね、リボンの下のところ
It has that kind of transparency.
そういう透け感があるの
Do you like it?
好きなの?
Yeah.
うん
Alright, it's time to go.
よっしゃ、クータイム
Were you surprised?
びっくりした?
Yeah.
うん
Can I touch you a little?
ちょっと触ってもいい?
Tsuntsun.
ツンツンって
Underwear, underwear.
下着です、下着
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
It tickles me.
くすぐったいって
Will the way I touch it change?
触り方変わるかな?
Yeah.
うん
Does that mean I should touch it properly?
ちゃんと触ったほうがいいってこと?
different.
違う
different?
違う?
Yeah.
うん
What should I do to get the correct answer?
正解はどうすればいいんだろう?
There is no correct answer.
正解なし
Isn't there a correct answer?
正解ない?
It's super smooth.
超すべすべだね
a,
あ、
I hid it.
隠 しちゃった
What's going on inside?
中はどうなってんの?
Is it okay to look inside?
中見ていいんでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
You said it was fine earlier.
いいって言ってたじゃん、さっき
Isn't it good?
いい んでしょ?
I'm really curious about that.
中気になるんだよね
Because it's a little hot.
ちょっと暑いから
Shall we take a look?
見 ちゃおうか
It's still white inside, too.
まだ真っ白だね、中も
Don't you get sunburned?
日焼けしないの?
do.
する
do?
する?
Yes, it's very white.
うん、すごい白いよ
So, you know.
で、あのさ
Who married Masaki Suda?
須田雅樹と結婚した人誰だっけ?
While you wait.
お待ちながら
They look similar.
似てるよね
Are you told?
言われる?
absolutely.
全く
Told or unsaid?
言われ、言われない?
Yeah.
うん
Are they similar?
似てる?
They don't look alike.
似てない
Super cute, seriously.
超可愛い、マジで
Down to the bottom.
下まで
Put your hands like this, behind your head and neck like this.
両手こうやってさ、頭の首の後ろでこうやって
Try putting it together.
組んでみて
yeah?
ん?
what?
何?
Too much.
もっちゃもっちゃ
I don't like it.
嫌
What?
何が?
I don't like it.
嫌
What do you dislike?
何が嫌なの?
picture?
え?
I don't like it, it's normal.
嫌だ、普通に
What?
何が?
I was just telling you to pick up your pen.
筆上げてって言ってただけだよ
Yeah, I don't like it.
うん、嫌だ
What is that?
それがなの?
Yeah.
うん
why?
なんで?
I don't like it.
嫌
tell me.
教えて
I just don't like it.
普通に嫌
I don't like it.
嫌
What?
何が?
So, please tell me why you don't like it.
で、なんで嫌か言ってくれたらいいよ
I just don't like it.
普通に嫌だ
No, what?
いや、何が?
I just don't like it.
普通に嫌だ
What can't be done?
何がとかない
I don't like it.
嫌だ
what?
何?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしいの?
What?
何が?
Yeah.
うん
What can't be done?
何がとかないのって
Do you just dislike it?
普通に嫌なの?
I just hate it, I just hate it.
嫌だけ、嫌だけ
You did it once.
やったじゃん、一回
Yeah.
うん
That's why it's good.
だからいいじゃん
Yeah.
うん
I thought I'd like to see it a little more.
もうちょっと、見たいなと思って
I don't like it.
嫌だ
You just said you didn't like it.
嫌だけって言ってたじゃん
I said you can take it.
取っていいよって
It doesn't matter where you are.
どこだったらいいんだじゃん
I don't like it anywhere.
どこも嫌
picture?
え?
I don't like it anywhere.
どこも嫌
She said that she would let me touch her beautiful body.
綺麗な体、触らせてくれるって言ってたじゃん
I hope you let me touch you.
触らせてくれるといいよって
I was just touching her underwear when I touched it.
下着、触ってたら触れちゃっただけじゃん
I wonder what kind of texture it has.
どういう質感なのかなって
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
yes.
はい
Well then, next time.
じゃあ、今度
picture?
え?
Look this way.
こっち向いて
what?
何?
Cut your face and put your hands on it.
顔を切って、そっちに手を出して
Goo more.
もっとグーって
Turn your head towards this one too.
こっちの方も顔を向ける
It's amazing and beautiful.
すごくて綺麗だね
Take your butt out.
お尻付き出して
Is it okay to take off your underwear?
下着取るのいいんでしょ?
I want to see it, so I'll stretch it out a little.
僕見たいからちょっと伸ばす
Because it's wrinkled.
シワになっちゃってるからさ
Scraps.
くずが
She's small and has a cute butt.
小ぶりで可愛いお尻してるね
Yeah.
うん
yeah?
ん?
what happened?
どうしたの?
absolute.
絶対
What, have you been using these underwear for a long time?
え、ここの下着、長く使ってるの?
Yeah.
うん
I don't know.
分かんない
It's already cute, now.
もう可愛いね、これで
yeah?
ん?
No way.
やだ
No?
やだ?
Yeah.
うん
Is it okay to change just a little?
ちょっとだけ変わっちゃダメ?
No way.
やだ
feel?
感じる?
Around here?
この辺?
no.
いや
I want to crumble.
くずがったい
Is it crap?
く ずがったい?
Just a little height.
ちょっとだけ高さ
Isn't it good?
いいでしょ?
It's a bit beautiful, body.
ちょっと綺麗だね、体
Hasn't it changed since middle school?
中学生くらいからもう変わんない?
Body shape.
体型
You understand, right?
分かるでしょ?
Your clothes size won't change at all, right?
服のサイズがもう何も変わんないでしょ?
It's small.
小ぶりな
It's really beautiful, really.
めっちゃ綺麗、ほんと
I can't see very well.
ちょっと よく見えないからさ
Raise your arms.
腕上げて
No.
いやだ
Is that not okay?
そっちはダメなの?
Is this good?
こっちはいいのに?
Yeah.
うん
Not good.
よくない
picture?
え?
Not good.
よくない
Isn't it good?
よくない?
picture?
え?
That's fine.
いいじゃん
No.
いやだ
Give me a hard time.
つんつんってしてあげ
No way.
やだ
No?
ダメ?
Yeah.
うん
Tsunha?
つんは?
No way.
やだ
No Tsun Tsun?
つんつんダメ?
No way.
やだ
Is Tsumu no good?
つむはダメ?
No way.
やだ
I wondered what would happen when I touched it.
じゃあどうなるかなと思って触ったら
Nothing.
なんのない
Nothing?
なんのない?
So can I try it?
じゃあ試していい?
No way.
やだ
What will happen?
どうなるか
Maybe nothing will happen.
なんも起こらないかもしれないけど
No way.
やだ
I just want to confirm the result that nothing happens.
なんも起こらないっていうとの結果をちょっと確認したいんだ
But.
けど
good.
いい
Well then, hear me.
じゃあ お聞こえ
Is this good?
こっちはいい?
What?
なんの?
Is that not okay?
そっちはダメなの?
Because it won't break.
そこは折れないんだから
That part is hard.
そ こは硬いんだからね
Huh?
あれ?
Isn't it okay?
いいんじゃないの?
Are you putting in effort?
力入ってる?
amazing.
すごい
What what?
なになに?
Isn't it okay?
いいんじゃないの?
I was just talking about shooting.
撮影だけで言ってたじゃん
I'll give it to you again for a plus.
プラスでまたあげるからさ
Do you want to join?
入りたい?
That part will break.
そこが折れるだって
Just touch it a little.
ちょっと触るだけだから
I haven't even done a tour yet.
まだツーンもしてないよ
Look at your fingers.
指見てみて
Because I'm not bored.
ツーンしてないから
good?
いい?
Does it hurt if you press hard?
強く押したら痛いでしょ?
It smelled.
臭がった
Look, look.
見て見て
You said nothing would happen.
なんも起こらないって言ってたよね
Please show me a little.
ちょっと見せてみて
What happened?
どうなった?
Nothing happened.
なんもなってないよ
Nothing has become normal.
普通になんもなってない
tickles.
くすぐったい
It started to emerge though.
浮 き出てきたけど
tickles.
くすぐったい
What do you mean when you say it came out?
浮き出てきたって言うのはどういうこと?
tickles.
くすぐったい
Don't hide it.
隠さないでさ
Show me.
見せてよ
You can't tell unless you take a close-up photo.
近くで撮んないと分かんない
How many plastic cups?
プラ何カップ?
tickles.
くすぐったい
How many cups?
何カップ?
Secret cup?
秘密カップ?
tickles.
くすぐったい
What should I do?
どうすればいい?
You don't have to do anything.
どうもしなくていいよ
What about this?
こっちは?
They seem to have different sensitivities.
感度違うらしいんだよね
on the right and left.
右と左で
Does that mean it's okay if it's not ticklish?
くすぐったくないのにすればいいってこと?
It's ticklish.
くすぐったいもん
Where should it be?
どこだったらいい?
Everything tickles.
全部くすぐったい
Should it be around here?
この辺だといい?
Everything tickles.
全部くすぐったい
You'll end up in that mode.
そういうモードになっちゃうよね
surely.
確かに
When I think about tickling, it seems like everything feels ticklish.
くすぐったいって思うと、全部くすぐったい感じちゃうみたいな
surely.
確かに
Is it like that?
そういう感じかな?
surely.
確かに
This isn't ticklish, right?
こっちはくすぐったくないでしょう?
surely.
確かに
How ticklish is it?
どこまでくすぐったくないか?
tickles.
くすぐったい
tickles?
くすぐったい?
I want to make sure it's not ticklish.
くすぐったくないか確認したい
tickles...
くすぐったい...
It's not ticklish, you know.
くすぐったくないでしょ、ほら
Hey.
ねえ
tickles.
くすぐったい
You're saying it's not ticklish.
くすぐったくないのに、と言ってるでしょ
This is how you turn on the power.
電源やるとこうやって
It's really tingling.
めっちゃゾワゾワする
This is effective for stiff shoulders.
肩こりとかに効くんだよ、これ
No, it's really scary.
いや、めっちゃゾワゾワする
Chochocho, no, no, no.
ちょちょちょ、なしなしなし
I started taking it all over.
全身取り始めた
real?
ほ んと?
I hate it, I hate it, I hate it.
嫌だ嫌だ嫌だ嫌だ
It really has been removed.
本当に取り外さってるね
I'm really bad at it.
め っちゃ 苦手
めっちゃ苦手
Wow, I really hate it.
うわ、めっちゃ嫌
No?
ダメ?
No.
ダメ
none.
なし
I know my skin is better.
肌のほうがいいってことが分かる
It tickles.
くすぐったいね
I have a smell fetish.
匂いフェチなんだよね
I'm making a face.
顔してる
No way.
やだ
Do you want a hug?
ハグしたいの?
tickles.
くすぐったい
く す ぐ った い
I haven't done anything.
なんもしてない
tickles.
くすぐったい
Be still, be still.
じっとして、じっと
I can't.
できない
like this.
こう
I haven't done anything.
なんもしてない
Seriously.
まじ
what?
何?
Why do you have to cry to move?
なん で 泣かなきゃ動くの?
Can you see it reflected?
映ってるの見える?
What?
なんだ?
なによ
Should we have a meeting?
打ち合ったらいい?
Just properly.
ちゃんとだけ
It's ticklish.
くすぐったいもん
Because I'm going out.
だって、出ちゃう
tickles.
くすぐったい
Lie.
嘘つけ
tickles.
くすぐったい
く すぐったい
tickles.
Hold still for a moment.
ちょっとじっとしてよ